<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Simple Voice Recorder</string>
    <string name="app_launcher_name">Gravador de voz</string>
    <string name="recording_saved_successfully">Gravação guardada</string>
    <string name="recording">Gravação</string>
    <string name="no_recordings_found">Não foram encontradas gravações\ncriadas por esta aplicação</string>
    <string name="no_recordings_in_folder_found">Não foram encontradas gravações\nna pasta selecionada</string>
    <string name="paused">Em pausa</string>

    <!-- Confirmation dialog -->
    <string name="delete_recordings_confirmation">Tem a certeza de que deseja apagar %s?</string>    <!-- Are you sure you want to delete 5 recordings? -->
    <plurals name="delete_recordings">
        <item quantity="one">%d gravação</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d gravações</item>
    </plurals>

    <!-- Settings -->
    <string name="try_hiding_notification">Tentar ocultar a notificação da gravação</string>
    <string name="save_recordings_in">Guardar gravações em</string>
    <string name="bitrate">Taxa de dados</string>
    <string name="record_after_launch">Iniciar gravação automaticamente ao iniciar a aplicação</string>

    <!-- FAQ -->
    <string name="faq_1_title">Can I hide the notification icon during recording?</string>
    <string name="faq_1_text">Well, it depends. While you use your device it is no longer possible to fully hide the notifications of apps like this.
        If you check the proper setting item, the app will do its best to hide it. You can hide it on the lockscreen though, if you disable the displaying of sensitive notifications in your device settings.</string>

    <!-- Strings displayed only on Google Playstore. Optional, but good to have -->
    <!-- App title has to have less than 50 characters. If you cannot squeeze it, just remove a part of it -->
    <string name="app_title">Simple Voice Recorder - Gravação de sons</string>
    <!-- Short description has to have less than 80 chars -->
    <string name="app_short_description">Aplicação para gravar discussões ou sons. Sem anúncios nem acesso à Internet</string>
    <string name="app_long_description">
        Ever wished you remember what the other person said? Or the task they gave you at a meeting? Wish no more. With this simple recorder you can record any audio really quickly.

        The app goes straight to the point, it contains no fancy features that you won\'t use. Just you and the voice recorder. It shows the current sound volume on a nice visualization that you can have a lot of fun with. Provides a really intuitive and clean user interface, not much can go wrong there.

        It offers a helpful player too so that you can listen to your recordings quickly, maybe rename or delete them.

        Contains no ads or unnecessary permissions. It is fully opensource, provides customizable colors.

        <b>Consulte o conjunto completo de aplicações Simple Tools aqui:</b>
        https://www.simplemobiletools.com

        <b>Facebook:</b>
        https://www.facebook.com/simplemobiletools

        <b>Reddit:</b>
        https://www.reddit.com/r/SimpleMobileTools
    </string>

    <!--
        Haven't found some strings? There's more at
        https://github.com/SimpleMobileTools/Simple-Commons/tree/master/commons/src/main/res
    -->
</resources>
